are recommending but we're also looking
at ICICI and Lombard and the Q4 numbers
I think the stock is under a bit of
pressure right now survey's here to tell
us more about that so we'll be over to
you
thanks so much for that I says hello mod
will be in Focus today that's because
the earnings were a mixed Bank the gdpi
which is the gross direct premium income
missed estimate but the pat beat
estimates and that was largely due to
higher investment income the gdpi was up
seven percent on a year-on-year basis
the net earned premium was up 12 on a
year on year basis the combined ratio
also remained elevated at 104 which was
in line with the estimates the company
continues to guide a combined ratio of
102 percent by fy25 the claims ratio was
also higher than estimates and that was
due to higher claims ratio in the motor
third-party portfolio the management
continued to remain cautious in the
motor business given the competitive
intensity now that combined with the
regulatory requirement of Bringing Down
the stake of promoter entity ICICI Bank
continues to be an overhang for the
stock brokerages also have a cautious
view on this Jeffries has a buy rating
but they've cut their Target price to
1560. they say for fy25 fi25 foreign you
have to watch out for the rice and cost
of reinsurance and also how industry
adapts to the expense of management rule
they trim their estimates by three to
five percent they further say that the
steak steak sale and the CEO succession
May limit the re-rating of the stock JP
Morgan has a neutral rating but they've
cut their Target price to 1160. they say
the motor portfolio is likely to remain
competitive and the comprehensive
product portfolio which is PNC may see
lower profitability due to increase in
reinsurance rates they don't have the
visibility to price in a beat of the
management guidance of 102 of combined
ratio by fy25
additionally Morgan Stanley has an
overweight with a Target price of 1400
UBS has a buy rating with a Target price
of 14 45 and nuama is the lowest amongst
all it has a whole rating with a Target
price of 1200.
uh survey thanks very much for that and
you can catch the management devices
here Lombard
CFO and chief risk officer the company
join us at 9 50 for a chat on the
performance so that's coming up later on
the show uh now we're racing to the
market open S6 is uh sorry the pre-open
is indicating an absolutely uh flatish
kind of style that's where rates have
settled on the Nifty and the sensex uh
but let's refocus on a few stocks Titan
is something we want to highlight once
again back to you well the two reasons
why Titan is in Focus today the first
one is quota constitutional equities has
written that their interactions with uh
so the franchise owners and the industry
suggest that the Titan management has
gone ahead and cut incentives
commissions that they give to their
franchisee owners by about 50 to 60
basis points or 100 basis points
depending on uh you know the nature of
the franchise that it is the impact of
this could be a positive 50 basis points
Improvement in their margins over the
next two years and over and above that
the company has anyway been uh you know
tightening the leash on costs itself
that's as far as the business is
concerned the second reason why I'm
watching is uh and more important from a
stock market standpoint remember when
the lens card deal it happened where
Adia had invested in the company we are
at CNBC TV 18 had posed the question
that will analysts now start describing
value to Titan's eye care business and
that's exactly what has happened clsa
has written and they believe that their
iCare business will go ahead and be a
group driver for the company and they've
valued the iCare business which was
previously not valued by analysts at 1.9
billion dollars so that's a big positive
as a result of which they've increased
the Target price on the target Titan as
well to about 31.50 odd rupees okay all
right thanks a lot for that while I'm
focusing on coal India JP Morgan they
have been positive on coal India and
they retain their weight stance they've
increased their target pressure around
290 from around 285 earlier they're
expecting that long-awaited FSA price
hike to come about given that the wage
hike has happened now the street is
focusing on FSA Air price hike as well
keep in mind that the last hike was in
January 2018 so it's been a long time
since we've seen the last tie if in fact
they can report stable earnings or maybe
higher than expected earnings then it'll
lead to uh you know higher dividends and
finally they point out that the FIS they
have been a little bit you know
skeptical on the stock but now they've
increased their holding telling you that
ESG discount is now behind and it
appears they're looking ahead given that
they've increased uh they're holding by
around 1.3 percent odd oh admitted in
time for an opening that's going to be
really flat right I mean not too much
expected anyway